let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the scope of a variable declared with var in javascript?",
    answer: "Global",
    options: [
        "Global",
        "Local",
        "Both",
        "var is a constant",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question:"What's the difference between '==' and '===' in JS?",
    answer: "== loose, === strict",
    options: [
        "== strict, === loose",
        "== loose, === strict",
        "=== objects, == arrays",
        " == strings, === numbers",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:"What is the syntax for an object in JavaScript?",
    answer: "{key: value, key: value}",
    options: [
        "{key: value, key: value}",
        "{value: key}",
        "[key, value, key, value]",
        "(key, value, key, value)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question:"How do you add an element to an array in JavaScript?",
    answer:  "myArray.push(element)",
    options: [
        "myArray[length] = element",
        "myArray.add(element)",
        "myArray.insert(element)",
        "myArray.push(element)",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question:  "How do you access an element in an array in JavaScript?",
    answer:  "myArray[index]",
    options: [
        "myArray.get(index)",
        "myArray[index]",
        "myArray.value(index)",
        "myArray.element",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question:  "How do you call a function in JavaScript?",
    answer:  "myFunction()",
    options: [
        "call myFunction()",
        "execute myFunction()",
        "run myFunction()",
        "myFunction()",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question:  "What is the function in JavaScript to convert a number to a string?",
    answer:  "toString()",
    options: [
        "toString()",
        "stringify()",
        "numberToString()",
        "convertToString()"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question:  "How to get the target element of an event in javascript?",
    answer:  "var target = event.target",
    options: [
        "var target = event.target",
        "var target = this",
        "var target = event.srcElement",
        "var target = event.currentTarget",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How to load data from local storage in javascript?",
    answer:  "loadStorage('key')",
    options: [
        "localStorage.setItem('key')",
        "loadStorage('key')",
        "localStorage.load('key')",
        "storage.load('key')",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the correct way to select a DOM element by its id? = document.",
    answer:  "getElementById('id')",
    options: [
        "getElementByTag('id')",
        "getElementsByID('id')",
        "querySelector('id')",
        "getElementById('id')",
    ]
  }
  ];